From my college days till now, my two-wheeler has
always supported me. Earlier, I used to enjoy
hanging out with friends and
going on long drives with my wife after marriage. But
now that our family has grown from two to four,
my ride too deserves to upgrade from a two-wheeler to a four-
wheeler. My only dream is to own
one. For this,
I need a reliable plan that will
give me a large sum of money at the right time. A
reliable plan that will support you in fulfilling all your responsibilities. ICICI
Prudential Life brings to you a
new-age plan, ICICI Prudential Sukh
Samriddhi, which will give you a
large sum of money at a fixed time so that you can
fulfill even your biggest dreams.
With ICICI Prudential Sukh Samriddhi,
you too can fulfill your dreams like Ramesh Agarwal. The
lumpsum option of this plan offers you many
benefits. By paying a premium of Rs. 50,000 every year for 10 years,
you will accumulate a huge corpus after 20 years.
On policy maturity, you will get tax-free funds
which you can use for a bright future for yourself and your family. For the
entire
policy term, you  Life cover also
protects your future and your
growing needs with
this ICC approach to happiness and prosperity that gives
you both the assurance of guaranteed returns and the
opportunity to grow, with
a trusted name to support you in every dream.
ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance
[Music]